## Hanna Nicolas, Sales Manager Enthusiast

Waterloo, +1 519 403 9508, +1 519 403 9508, hannanicolasca@gmail.com

PROFILE	Confident young professional with a passion for learning and development. More than six years in the sales industry. I am committed to continuous improvement and driving team success. I have managed teams of up to 6 people. I care about improving my community, so I always seek to take the initiative in different fields, such as charity and supporting my closest colleagues' personal and professional growth.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Dec 2015 — Jul 2017	Cashier, New Shop			Carupano, Venezuela
	<ul> <li>Handled large amount of money and multiple transactions.</li> <li>Was able to work under pressure.</li> </ul>			
Aug 2017 — Dec 2018	Salesman, New Shop			Carupano, Venezuela
	<ul> <li>Helped customers to get the right fit and supply them with what they wanted.</li> <li>Served multiple customers at the same time.</li> <li>Salesman of the year</li> </ul>			
Jan 2019 — Jan 2021	Manager, New shop			Carupano, Venezuela
	<ul> <li>Managed a team of 6 people.</li> <li>Same responsabilities + new responsabilites such as checking inventory, buying new products, train new staff.</li> </ul>			
EDUCATION				
Sep 2014 — Jul 2019	High School Diploma, UEP "Simon Bolivar"  Carupano, Venezue			Carupano, Venezuela
	Graduated among the best in the class			
Sep 2019 — Dec 2021	System Engineering Diploma, Universidad Santa Maria  Puerto La Cruz, Venezuela			
Sep 2022 — Aug 2024	Computer programming, Conestoga College Waterloo			
	I am currently studying computer programming. I have some basic knowledge in C#, HTML, JavaScript, and some SQL.			
SKILLS	Ability to Work Under Pressure	Expert	Computer Skills	Expert
	Fast Learner	Expert	Good Communication	Expert
	Leadership	Expert	Ability to Multitask	Expert
	Ability to Work in a Team	Expert	Excellent Customer Service Sk	ills Expert
LANGUAGES	Spanish; Castilian	Native speaker	English	Highly proficient
CERTIFICATIONS				
Mar 2022 — Mar 2022	110/160 - Duolingo English Test Waterloo			
	According to Duolingo's scale, this result is equivcalent to a CERF B2 level			
	Open certificate	-		
Mar 2022 — Apr 2022	English for Academic Studie	es		Waterloo
	English certificate from Conestoga	College		